howickvillage.co.za 2017-10-04

# Privacy Policy - HowickVillage.co.za | HowickVillage.co.za

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, (this enables you to place an advert on the notice board and submit an image to the gallery) or fill out the contact form.

When registering on our site, you will be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

 **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to this site.  
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

 **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website.

These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Online privacy protection**  
We will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.. All users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

 **Changes to our privacy policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

 **Contacting us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

Site Administrator  
HowickVillage.co.za  
PO Box 1374  
Hilton  
3245

or

Email: [info@howickvillage.co.za](mailto:info@howickvillage.co.za)
